威尔 · 森塔斯: 还有什么其他的方法可以做到，内置函数是什么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What's another way that
I can, what's a built-in function of
的输出将永远是一个空对象？
JavaScript whose output will be
an empty object forevermore?
是的，亚当，拜托？
Yeah, Adam, please?
亚当: 反对，创造。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Object.create.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 反对。创建，非常好，来自亚当，是的，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Object.create,
very nice, from Adam, yeah, spot-on.
用户3使用 object.create。
User3 using object.create.
这是 JavaScript 中的一个内置函数。
This is a built-in function in JavaScript.
它会给我们一些细粒度的，这是一个书呆子的词。
It's gonna give us later on some
fine-grained, it's such a nerdy word.
给我们一些对对象的细粒度控制。
Give us some fine-grained
control over our object.
但我只想让你们知道，这是唯一的事情
But I just want you all to know for
now, it's only thing
就我们的对象本身而言，就是返回一个空对象。
in terms of our object itself, that it
does, is return out an empty object.
右手边这里。
So right hand side here.
我们先从左边开始。
Well let's just declare
left hand side here first.
轮到你了，凯拉。
Over to you Kayla.
等等，为什么我总是跳过最后一个字母？
Hold on,
why do I always skip the last letter?
这很有趣，不是吗？
It's very interesting, right?
一定是我在加速我的写作。
It must be me trying to
accelerate my writing.
好吧。
All right, yeah.
先从左手边开始，吉拉。
Left-hand side first Kyla.
我们宣布一个常量用户3。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: We're declaring
a constant User3.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，用户3，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, user3, excellent.
右手边的人会马上从我们这里回来什么，凯拉？
Right-hand side is gonna immediately
return fro us what Kyla?
一个空物体。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: An empty object.
一个空的物体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: An empty object.
就是这样，人们。
That is it people.
所以即使我愿意，威尔 · 森塔斯: 甚至
And so even if I were to,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Even
如果我进入了那些幻想,
if I were to pass into those parethens,
你可能认为那些有知识的父母是聪明的 md。
you might think those parethens
having knowledge is wise MD.
我可以传入一个对象，这个对象充满了各种属性,
I could pass in an object in there
full of objects full of properties,
我不管我通过它，我可以通过一个麻木任何我想要的。
I don't matter what I pass it,
I could pass in a numb anything I want.
它将返回一个空对象。
It's going to return out an empty object.
现在，这个空对象可能具有一些隐藏属性，这取决于我们
Now that empty object might have some
hidden properties on depending on what we
进入，或隐藏的财产。
pass in, or hidden property on.
但它总是一个空对象，没有直接属性。
But it's always an empty object,
no direct properties on it.
然后，我们将分配到它的 name 属性，即值。
We then assign through to it name
property, which is the value.
伊娃学校已经储存在它。
Eva school which has stored in it.
9和再增量方法，这是一个函数。
9 and again increment
method which is a function.
让我们来确认一下我是否能做我自己的重要事情。
Let's just confirm whether I
can do my own important thing.
3. increment，Todd 我能帮你吗？
Use3.increment, Todd can I assist you?
我的第一次是一次又一次，他是我的绿色从我看这里。
My first time ever was again and again and
he's my green from I look up here.
是的，绿色的杯子。
Yeah green for the cup.
我在哪里可以找到 user3，Todd？
Where do I look for user3, Todd?
托德: 在对象存储器里。
&gt;&gt; Todd: In the Object memory.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 进化记忆，是吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Evo memory, isn't it?
托德: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Yes.
为什么我要寻找增量？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Why do I look for
increments?
Todd: 在 user3对象中。
&gt;&gt; Todd: In the user3 object.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我找到了吗。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And do I find it.
托德: 是的 威尔 · 森特斯: 如果我这么做。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: If I do.
抓住它的代码和执行它是一个梦想成真。
Grab its code and
execute it be was a dream come true.
梦想成真了。
It's a dream come true.
我做的这个是面向对象的。
I done this is an object oriented.
我有数据和函数，数据方法一起工作
I've got data and functions,
data methods that work together and
不要和其他东西一起工作。
don't work with other stuff.
现在，严格地说，我可以在其他领域使用这些函数。
Now, strictly I could always use
these function in other areas.
所以它不是严格意义上的保护
So it's not strictly kind of protected but
for
一般来说，我们可以走了。
general purposes,
we're pretty much good to go.
但是我的代码越来越重复，我们违反了什么原则，瑞安？
But I codes getting repetitive,
what principles are we breaking Ryan?
瑞恩: 画画 威尔 · 句子: 抽签,
&gt;&gt; Ryan: Draw.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Draw,
我不想重复你的话，这些命令都是我们手工制作的。
I don't repeat yourself,
we hand crafting these orders.
每次用户登录,
Every time a user logs in,
我们得把幕后的开发商都写出来。
we're gonna have to write out fully the
developers behind the scenes filling out.
它们的特性。
Their properties.
无论何时，只要我们的代码被多次执行，比如添加属性。
Whenever we have code that is being done
multiple times, like adding properties.
当我们一遍又一遍地写代码的时候，我们倾向于做什么？
What do we tend to do whenever we're doing
lines of code, again and again and again?
我们用什么把他们包起来，托德？
What do we wrap them up in, Todd?
托德: 我会归纳函数，抽象它，然后向下。
&gt;&gt; Todd: I would generalize function,
abstract it, down.
威尔 · 句子: 加入一个函数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Put in a function.
保存它一次又一次地使用。
Save it once use again and again.
唯一需要修改的部分是 Parson 作为要指定的输入
And the only bits you want to change have
those be Parson as inputs to specify
当你运行这个函数的时候，它到底要做什么。
when you run the function,
what it's actually going to do.
是的，但是对付托德正是我们要做的。
Yes but
on Todd is exactly what we're gonna do.
人们的解决方案之一就是
And folks solution one for and
我只是想再钻探一次，以防人们真的没有这种感觉。
I just wanna drill one more time in case
people aren't really really feeling this.
这是一个梦想成真
It is a dream come true for
当我写100,000行代码的时候，当我说我的数据。
me when I'm writing with 100,000 lines
of code that when I say my data.
我的功能并不神秘。
There's no mystery as to
what my functionality is.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我的功能是什么
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well, what my
functionality is that will apply to that
数据，因为看看那些人，就在那里。
data because look at that folk,
it's right there.
可以应用于该数据的函数。
The function that could
be applied to that data.
一旦你开始思考这个范式,
And once you start thinking
in terms of this paradigm,
把你的数据和功能放在一起。
of putting your data and
the functionality together in one place.
用户3所需要的所有功能都在这里。
All the functionality I could ever
need for the user3 is right there.
一旦你开始以这种方式思考，你就开始经常这样做。
Once you start thinking in that way,
you start doing this a lot.
您开始将应用程序中的所有内容都考虑为
You start thinking of everything
in your applications as
这个特殊功能的功能数据是什么？
what's the data in the functionality
connected to that particular feature?
这真的非常非常好。
It's actually really, really nice.
这并不像我强调的那样受欢迎
It's not as popular as why
I'm really emphasizing
这是关于理解 JavaScript 的原则。
this is about understanding
the principles in JavaScript.
让我们这样做，我们使用的各地。
Let us do this,
which we use all over the place.
因为面向对象编程的范例并不是越来越流行
Because the paradigm of object oriented
programming is not as popular increasingly
作为函数式编程风格，但是非常惊人，非常直观。
as the functional programming style,
but are amazing, really intuitive.
构造应用程序的思维方式，应用程序就是数据。
Way of thinking about structuring
an application, application is data.
用户得分，无论是什么功能，改变用户得分的能力,
User scores, whatever functionality,
the ability to change that user score,
把它放在一起。
put it together.
看看这个，就是这个。
And look at it, is that right there.
很漂亮，但我们正在进行移动时间。
Beautiful, but we're doing a mobile time.
现在让我们来创建对象，保存一次。
So now let's do the work of
creating the object, save it once.
创建对象，然后想用多少次就用多少次。
Create the objects and
then use it as many times as we like.
这正是我们要做的。
That's exactly what we're gonna do here.
生成我们的对象，生成甚至不是正确的词。
Generate our objects,
generate isn't even the right word.
使用函数创建并返回对象。
Create and
return our objects using a function.
这个解决方案，一个人最终会被证明是站不住脚的。
This solution one people going
to turn out to be untenable.
你永远不可能在实践中使用它，但它可以让我们走很长的路。
You can never use it in practice,
but it gets us a long way there.
我们所做的一切都是为了让这个过程更有效率。
Everything else we do it's just about
making this much, much more efficient.
在这一点上，我已经给了你一个提示。
I have given you a hint there.